你知道哈努曼的故事吗?
Do you know the story of Hanuman?
没有?
No?
看看这个。
Look at this.
看。
Look.
故事是这样的……当哈努曼还小的时候……很少的……他很饿。
The story goes... When Hanuman was little... Very little... He was very hungry.
所以饿了。
So hungry.
就像你一样!
Just like you!
他可以吃森林里的任何水果。
He could have eaten any fruit in the forest.
但有什么东西对他下了魔咒。
But something cast a spell on him.
高高在树之上。
High above the trees.
那是一个又大又多汁的芒果。
It was a big juicy mango.
所以闪亮。
So shiny.
看看这个。
Look at this.
你知道他做了什么吗?
Do you know what he did?
哈努曼飞上了天空。
Hanuman took to the skies.
径直走向那个水果。
Straight towards that fruit.
那个多汁的芒果。
That juicy mango.
所以闪亮。
So shiny.
却发现……那不是芒果，而是灼热的太阳。
Only to discover... that it wasn't a mango but the burning, hot sun.
众神听说了这件事……并聚集起来惩罚他。
The gods heard of this... and gathered to punish him.
他们给了他一个教训。剥夺了小哈努曼的能力
They taught him a lesson... and stripped young Hanuman of his powers.
然后发生了什么，妈妈?
And then what happened, Ma?
没有他妈的规则!
There are no fucking rules!
战斗!
Fight!
长官，老虎，长官。
Sir, Tiger, sir.
国王Kobra !国王Kobra !国王Kobra !
King Kobra! King Kobra! King Kobra!
老虎，我爱你!
Tiger, I love you!
国王Kobra !国王Kobra !
King Kobra! King Kobra!
国王Kobra !国王Kobra !国王Kobra !国王Kobra !
King Kobra! King Kobra! King Kobra! King Kobra!
哇!
Whoo!
-晚上好。
- Good evening.
这就是我要说的。
That's what I'm talking about.
欢迎来到老虎庙。
Welcome to Tiger's Temple.
这是一个神圣的地方。
This is a sacred space.
因为我们当中有些人是穆斯林。
Because some of us here are Muslim.
我们有些人是印度教徒。
Some of us are Hindu.
妈的，也许有个秘密的基督徒藏在椽子下面。
Fuck, maybe there's a closet Christian hiding somewhere there under the rafters.
但我们这里只崇拜一个神
But we here all worship one god:
印度卢比!
the Indian rupee!
胜利者，野兽的杀手，-科布拉国王!
The winner, the killer of the beast, - King Kobra!
看看这个疯子。看看这个。
Look at this maderchod. Look at this.
这就是胜利的味道。
That's the smell of victory right there.
-你闻到了吗?
- Do you smell it?
因为我他妈的闻到了!
'Cause I fucking smell it!
这是一个冠军。这是……
This is a champion. This is...
该死的，伙计们。多么美妙的一晚啊?
Fucking hell, guys. What a night, eh?
你听到了吗?他们恨死你了。
You hear that? They fucking hate you.
这是不可思议的。
It's incredible.
多么美好的夜晚。
What a night.
萨里珊，这是什么鬼肚子?
Sarishan, what's this fucking stomach?
太多萨莫萨了。你是蜥蜴王，不是萨莫萨王，明白吗?
Too many samosas. You're the Lizard King, not the fucking Samosa King, okay?
这该死的水龙头!
This fucking tap!
阿齐兹，我手上的水龙头又掉了。
Aziz, the fucking tap came off in my hands again, man.
到这里来。
Come here.
看这里。那是什么?
Look here. What's that?
那他妈一直开着。你知道我为此要付多少水费吗?
That fucking stays on. You know what my water bill is for that?
把该死的水龙头修好。请。
Fix the fucking tap. Please.
阿齐兹，把它修好，兄弟。请。
Aziz, just fix it, brother. Please.
我他妈只要一点干净的地方。
I ask just for a little bit of fucking cleanliness.
注意一点个人卫生。是的,什么?
A little bit of personal hygiene. Yes, what?
-是的。好吧。
- Yeah. All right.
别一下子花光了，好吗?
Don't spend it all at once, eh?
老虎。老虎，这是一半。
Tiger. Tiger, this is half.
怎么啦？这是你上次得到的。
What? That's what you got last time.
怎么，你存钱是为了找个更好的地方住吗?
What, are you saving for a better place to live?
你想要另外50%，你就得流血。
You want another 50%, you bleed.
这就是为什么它被称为流血奖励。
That's why it's called the bleed bonus.
我需要那笔钱。
I need that money.
然后跳舞。
Then dance.
别那样看着我。
Don't look at me like that.
你选的名字。
You chose the name.
你就像那些小猴子，你知道，在市场上…穿着粉红色的小裙子。
You're like those little monkeys, you know, in the marketplace that go... with a little pink skirt.
这是你的。
That's you.
上演一出戏，拿到钱。
Put on a show, get the money.
有成百上千的人会做这件事，嗯——成百上千——等着取代你的位置，如果你不适合做这件事的话。
There's hundreds of folks out there that'll do this, eh-- hundreds-- waiting to take your place if this isn't for you.
永生，获得不朽。
To live eternal, and gain immortality.
神的神圣礼物，来自巴巴沙克提。
A sacred gift of the Gods, from Baba Shakti.
爸爸生命力。
Baba Shakti.
大师，和平之人，国家的雄狮。
Guru, man of peace, the nation's lion.
出身贫寒，却不为贫寒所困。
Born to poverty but not held captive by it.
事实上，Baba Shakti现在更可能出现在精英的寺庙里，而不是在众神的寺庙里，与有钱有势的人擦肩而过。
Indeed, Baba Shakti is now likely to be seen in the temples of the elite than at the temples of the gods, rubbing shoulders with the rich and powerful.
这些都是一个人的简单行为吗?我把政治留给政治家。
Are these the simple actions of a man made good... I leave politics to the politicians.
…还是通过支持有争议的主权党开始推动政治权力?
...or the start of a push for political power through his endorsement of the controversial Sovereign Party?
如果我看到一个敬畏上帝的人在为印度做好事，我会支持他。
If I see a God-fearing man who is doing good for India, I will support him.
他否认了有关他的工厂……幸运仔，最近怎么样?
He has dismissed rumors that his factory... Lucky, how's things?
头等舱，兄弟。
First class, bro.
老板，给他来份芒果奶油冻。
Boss, get him a Mango Frooti.
嗯!要双份的。
Eh! Make it a double.
所以呢?
So?
幸运，幸运，幸运。
Lucky, Lucky, Lucky.
这就是你想要的人。
This is who you want.
奎妮·卡普尔，万王之王。
Queenie Kapoor, the queen of Kings.
星期五下午，她在Body Tonic做了按摩和足疗。
Friday afternoon, she had a massage and pedicure at Body Tonic.
大多数早晨，她都会在意大利咖啡馆停下来喝咖啡。
Most of the mornings, she stops at a Café d'Italia for coffee.
——环意大利自行车赛”?-是的。
- D'Italia? - Yeah.
她明天会在那里。
She'll be there tomorrow.
但祝你从她嘴里套出什么来。
But good luck getting anything out of her.
她真是个狠角色。
She's a real hard-ass.
-阿育吠陀智慧-好的。
-Ayurvedic wisdom - Okay.
-已经有几千年的历史了。-干得好。
- is thousands of years old. - Good job.
我们凭什么质疑诸神?
Who are we to question the gods?
毗湿奴，拉克希米，湿婆!50卢比。
Vishnu, Lakshmi, Shiva! For fifty rupees.
——是的。-在餐桌上，这就像一个口头契约。
- Yes. - On the dinner table, it was like a verbal contract.
我没有邮件。
I don't have any mail.
求你了，夫人，我两天没吃东西了。
Please, madam, I haven't eaten in two days.
求你了，求你了，夫人。
Please, please, madam.
-拜托，拜托，夫人。
- Please, please, madam.
——我……噢!-我的天啊。你怎么能让这些人进来?
- I'm... Ow! - Oh, my God. How can you allow these guys here?
你经营的是什么地方?
What kind of a place are you running?
♬跑，里基，跑，跑，跑，跳，跳，来
♪ Run, Ricky, run, run, run, jump, jump, come ♪
♬他们来了，跑啊，跑啊，跑啊! - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -
♪ Here they come, run, run, run, run ♪ - -♪ Gun with the drum, bum bitty bum ♪
♬瘫在后备箱里，我的城市走了
♪ Slump in the trunk, my city go ♪
♬哑，哑，哑，哑，151朗姆酒和一个钝的♬
♪ Dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb, 151 rum and a blunt ♪
♬年轻…麻木，麻木，麻木，他得到了一把小枪
♪ Young ... numb, numb, numb and he got a little gun ♪
♬一个小杀手真的只是为了好玩
♪ A little bitty killer really doin' it for fun ♪
♬给他一点，他就会得到一个…完成♪
♪ Give him a little bit and he'll get a ... done ♪
-♬上帝之子，上帝之子…♪
- ♪ Son of a god, son of a... ♪
♬女人和男人的儿子，儿子的儿子，在一个沉没的深渊
♪ Son of woman and man, son of a son, in a sunken abyss ♪
♬召唤一个计划，请带上一个剧本
♪ Summon a plan, please come with a script ♪
♬掩护我的背，掩护我的人，请随闪电战而来
♪ Cover my back, cover man, please come with the blitz ♪
♬看数据，我就像个魔术师
♪ Look at the stats, JID like a magician ♪
♪……这是真的…我为此付出了鲜血
♪ ... that, this some real-ass ... I paid blood for this ♪
♬从政府那里拿走奶酪
♪ Taking cheese from the government ♪
♬有虫子的麦片盒
♪ Cereal boxes with the bugs in it ♪
♬我的兄弟，这是我的兄弟……♪
♪ Hand-me-down, this my brother brother... ♪
♬跑，里基，跑，跑，跑，跳♬-♬跳，来，他们来了，跑，跑，跑，跑
♪ Run, Ricky, run, run, run, jump ♪ - ♪ Jump, come, here they come, run, run, run, run ♪
♬鼓着枪，小屁屁
♪ Gun with the drum, bum bitty bum ♪
♬瘫在后备箱里，我的城市走了♬-♬哑，哑，哑，哑，151朗姆酒和一个钝的♬
♪ Slump in the trunk, my city go ♪ - ♪ Dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb, 151 rum and a blunt ♪
♬年轻…麻木，麻木，麻木，他得到了一把小枪
♪ Young ... numb, numb, numb and he got a little gun ♪
♬一个小杀手真的只是为了好玩
♪ A little bitty killer really doin' it for fun ♪
♬给他一点，他就会得到一个…♪
♪ Give him a little bit and he'll get a... ♪
——夫人?
- Madam?
是吗?
Yeah?
你在哪里找到的?
Where did you find this?
一些人在意大利咖啡馆附近的JV路争夺它。
Some men were fighting over it next to, uh, JV Road near Café d'Italia.
我想冲进去，但是…他们反击了，然后…-拿着这个。-我…我不…我不要施舍。
I tried to rush in, and, uh, um... they fought back and, uh... - Take this. - I-I... I don't... I don't want charity.
我需要的是…是一份工作。
Wh-What I need is a... is a job.
这是金。
This is Kings.
我们只是不招街上的人。
We just don't hire off the street.
你的推荐信呢?
Where's your references?
-你的简历?嗯?
- Your CV? Hmm?
听着，我没时间跟你说这些。
Look, I don't have time for all this.
拿着它走吧。
Take it and go.
这一点。
This.
这是我的简历。
There's my CV.
这是漂白。
That's bleach.
化工、石油。
Chemical, oil.
把没人愿意做的工作给我。
Give me the job no one wants to do.
我来做。
I'll do it.
没有投诉。
No complaint.
我只知道这些。
This is all I know.
是的。
Yeah.
不。呃，不，不。听。
No. Uh, no, no. Listen.
我其实很喜欢这个来自印度尼西亚的。
I actually liked this one from Indonesia.
她破门而入了吗?
Is she broken in?
不，没关系，我只是想知道，呃…我们多快能拿到她的证件?
No, th-that's fine, but I just want to know if, uh... How quickly can we get her papers?
嗯?
Hmm?
任何在墙外说话的人，任何忘记自己位置的人，都不会有好下场。
Anyone who talks outside these walls, anyone who forgets their place, it doesn't turn out well for them.
理解吗?
Understood?
理解。
Understood.
一次。
Once more.
哦，上帝，我崇拜你。
Oh God, I worship you.
我只崇拜你。
I only worship you.
你是最强大的。
You are the most powerful one.
你是我的救世主。
You are my saviour.
我只崇拜你。
I only worship you.
你让我们微笑，让我们的心充满爱。
You make us smile and fill our hearts with love.
用眼睛，用耳朵。
With our eyes, with our ears.
在我们的嘴边，我们说着你的名字。
On our lips, we say your name.
我昼夜歌颂你。
I sing your praise, day and night.
我崇拜你。
I worship you.
新来的，是吧?
New guy, huh?
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
鲍比。
Bobby.
嗯。
Hmm.
戴好你的帽子。
Wear your cap properly.
我们可不想让你的阴毛出现在咖喱里…鲍比。
We don't want one of your pubes in the curry... Bobby.
我想我们以前见过，对吧?
I think we met before, right?
我不这么认为。
I-I don't think so.
你喜欢龙舌兰酒吗，鲍比?
You like tequila, huh, Bobby?
Patrón，唐·胡里奥，照片里有乔治·克鲁尼的那个?
Patrón, Don Julio, the one with George Clooney in the photo?
我只是想洗碗，好吗?
I just want to clean the dishes, okay?
可口可乐吗?吗啡?摇头丸吗?
Coke? Morphine? MDMA?
阿方索，我跟你说过很多次别再骚扰我的员工了。
Oi, Alphonso, eh, I've told you many times to stop hassling my staff.
-质量控制，伙计。
- Quality control, man.
总有一天你会为此感谢我的。
You're gonna thank me for this one day.
冷静点，鲍比。
Stay cool, Bobby.
保持冷静，好吗?
Stay cool, hmm?
小心我的腿，伙计。
Watch my fucking leg, man.
一个正常的paan。
One regular paan.
再来一杯拉朱特餐。
And a Raju Special.
狮子!
Lion!
是的。
Yes.
带他。
Take him.
我可以骑在他的肩膀上吗?
Can I go on his shoulders?
三轮车怎么样，小混蛋?带他!
How about a rickshaw, little bastard? Take him!
固体。
Solid.
来了。
Come.
你有什么?
What you got?
——槟榔。
- Paan.
进入。
Get inside.
这就是你的全部吗?
Is this all you got?
是的。
Yeah.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
因为我的每个祈祷都得到了回应。
'Cause I got an answer to every prayer.
你喜欢约翰·威克?因为这是刚收到的。
You like John Wick? 'Cause this just came in.
是的。
Yeah.
创科实业。
The TTI.
和电影里的枪一样。
Same gun from the movie.
但是中国制造。
But made in China.
——繁荣。
- Boom.
我想要一些小而有效的东西。
I want something small but effective.
…38口径的左轮手枪。
...38 caliber revolver.
它有点重，但很有冲击力。
It's a little bit heavy, but it's got a lot of thump.
你得离得很近。
You need to be pretty close.
接近就好。
Close is good.
我买了。
I'll take it.
工作人员入口。副本。
Staff entrance. Copy.
副本。员工入口安全。
Copy. Staff entrance secured.
嗯?
Huh?
你想回去为了500卢比在街上卖命吗?
You want to go back to selling your ass on the street for 500 rupees?
我带你进来，你就这样报答我吗?
I brought you in, and this is how you repay me?
嗯?
Huh?
-好的，好的。别哭了。
- Okay, okay. Don't cry.
-别哭。
- Don't cry.
伊拉尼医生一回来，我们就来处理。
As soon as Dr. Irani's back, we'll take care of it.
是吗?
Yeah?
你他妈的要杀了我了，拉胡尔。
You're fucking killing me, Rahul.
-不不不嗯。
- No, no, no. Uh-uh.
听我说……你给伊夫吉尼打电话，让那混蛋另找线人。
Listen to me... You call Evgeni and tell that motherfucker to find another source.
我造就了你!
I made you!
现在你觉得你可以坐在我肩膀上对着我耳朵撒尿了吗?
Now you think you can sit on my shoulders and piss in my ear?
他们他妈的都是。他妈的。
They're fuck all. Fuck all.
他妈的。你懂"去他妈的"吗?
Fuck all. You understand "fuck all"?
不，不，不。不,不。听着,听着。
No, no, no. No, no. Listen, listen.
我要保护自己的名誉，明白吗?
I have a reputation to protect, understand?
你他妈的有什么毛病?
What the fuck is your problem?
我跟你说过多少次了，快敲门进来…对不起。尼西特说你需要我。
How many times do I have to tell you fucking knock on the door and enter... Sorry. Nishit said you needed me.
我要你学点礼貌，你这杂种小山羊。
I need you to learn some manners, you inbred little goat fucker.
拉胡尔，我回头打给你。
Rahul, I'll have to call you back.
听着，去纳吉布买些克什米尔的雪花。
Listen, go to Naqeeb and pick up some Kashmiri snowflake.
好东西，好吗?不要那些廉价的东西。
Good stuff, okay? None of that cheap shit.
但问题是，质量控制不好。
But the problem is, uh, quality control, it's no good.
纳吉布对我有意见，知道吗?
Naqeeb has some issue with me, you know?
我不知道这是基督教和穆斯林之间的关系，还是别的什么，但是……-嗨。
I don't know whether it's the Christian-Muslim thing - or what, but... - Hey.
——你。面对墙壁。
- You. Face the wall.
你他妈在说什么?
What the fuck are you talking about?
告诉Naqeeb，如果马吃得好，我们再给Rana酋长买一些。
Tell Naqeeb, if the maal is good, - we'll buy some more for Chief Rana.
周末前把它整理好。
Get it sorted by the weekend.
他和他的孩子们一起来。
He is coming with his boys.
-嘿，阿方索——嗯?
- Hey, Alphonso. - Hmm?
只有最好的才能为贵宾服务。- - - - - - -是的。明白了。
Only the best to serve the VIPs. - -Yeah. Got it.
阿方索。阿方索。
Alphonso. Alphonso.
你和奎妮相处得不错吧?她真的很尊重你。
Hey, uh, good job with Queenie, huh? She really respects you.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
听着，如果你…如果你……听着，如果你需要贵宾的帮助…嘿，新来的…你知道蠼螋在这里会怎么样吗?
Um, look, if you... if you... Look, if you need any help with the VIPs... Hey, new guy... You know what happens to earwigs around here?
你什么也听不见，什么也看不见。明白了吗?
You hear nothing, you see nothing. Got it?
听着，我只是想说，如果你需要有人去做这件事……-我看起来像需要你这样的人帮忙吗?
Look, I'm just saying, if you need someone to go in - and do the job... - Does it look like I need some help from someone like you?
-嗨。-有那么…搞什么鬼，伙计?
- Hey. - Is there so... What the fuck, man?
好吧,好吧。我很抱歉。
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
听着，你想赚钱吗?
Look, you want to make some money?
保证吗?
Guaranteed?
-继续。——好的。
- Go on. - Okay.
嗯…今晚来这里吧。
Uh... come to this place tonight.
把赌注押在汗身上。你会大赚一笔的。
Bet on Khan. You'll make a killing.
你他妈怎么知道?
How the fuck do you know?
我会和他决斗的。
I-I'll be fighting him.
滚蛋。
Fuck off.
猴子将赢得前两回合，并在第三回合倒下。
The monkey will win the first two rounds and go down in the third.
这对你有什么好处?
What's in it for you?
我想升职。
I want a promotion.
♬你他妈说什么，毛希?♪
♪ What the fuck did you say, Maushi? ♪
♬Kay bolli?bolli凯?♪
♪ Kay bolli? Kay bolli? ♪
♬你他妈说什么，毛希?♪
♪ What the fuck did you say, Maushi? ♪
-♬凯·博利?♪
- ♪ Kay bolli? ♪
♬都是痴人说梦
♪ Are mavshi chi gaand ♪
♬切拉·巴格·南塔·巴格
♪ Chehra bagh nantar bhaand ♪
♬Maazi makdachi jaat zaaloy khulla sand♬
♪ Maazi makdachi jaat zaaloy khulla sand ♪
♬Vikun khau shakto tuze akkhe ghar daaik zara♬
♪ Vikun khau shakto tuze akkhe ghar daar aik zara ♪
-阿尼老和尚气季♬-钻他!就是这样!好了!
- ♪ Ani Old monk chi quarter ♪ - Drill him! That's it! Nice!
♬波尔塔波尔塔瓶子扎莉♬
♪ Bolta bolta bottle zaali ♪
♬贾拉·达曼，帕西亚·卡丽!♪
♪ Jara daman, padshyal khaali! ♪
我爱你，爱你，爱你
♪ Bhakkam sharir pan fakt ata hadke rahli ♪
杀了他，孩子!
♪ Tari dokyavar madke bhari kaa ♪ -Kill him, boy!
-♬Karan roz chi zhavzhav♬-是的!
- ♪ Karan roz chi zhavzhav ♪ - Yes!
♬dochkyala tras…♪
♪ An dochkyala tras... ♪
-它!
-Get it!
钻他!别光站在那儿!
Drill him! Don't just stand there!
退后，打他!
Get back, drill him!
打我!打我!
Hit me! Hit me!
困难!
Harder!
来吧!
Come on!
困难!打我!
Harder! Hit me!
别光站在那儿，伙计!
Don't just stand there, mate!
给他点金刚的东西。
Give him some of that Kong shit.
-当然!他妈的是的!
- Fucking yes! Fucking yes!
他妈的是的!哇!你这该死的美人!
Fuck yes! Whoo! You fucking beauty!
Mwah !
Mwah!
把这该死的猴子弄下来。
Get this fucking monkey off here.
伙计们，把猴子弄下来。
Guys, get the monkey off here.
胜利者，野兽的杀手，谢尔汗!
The winner, the killer of the beast, Sher Khan!
♬我不在乎谁对谁错
♪ I don't care who's wrong or right ♪
♬我真的不想再吵架了
♪ I don't really wanna fight no more ♪
♬说得太多了，宝贝……♪
♪ Too much talking, babe... ♪
确保饮料永远不会干涸。
Make sure the drinks never dry up.
眼睛盯着地面，除非有人叫你，否则你就会像屁股里塞了辣椒一样赶紧过去。
Eyes to the ground unless someone calls you, then you will get over there like you got a chili up your asshole.
看到了吗?那是国防部长。
You see that? That's the defense minister.
他总是吃蘑菇牛排，然后玩3p。
He always has a mushroom steak followed by a threesome.
这只喜欢看。
This one just likes to watch.
但他是税务局局长，所以什么都可以，你知道吗?
But he's the head of the tax office, so anything is allowed, you know?
晚安，古普塔先生。
A very good evening, Mr. Gupta.
希望你过得愉快。
Hope you are having a good time.
享受。
Enjoy.
肮脏的混蛋。
Filthy bastard.
♬来吧，人们，你相信爱情吗?♪
♪ Come on, people, do you believe in love? ♪
♬你必须有所坚持，否则你会被任何东西绊倒
♪ You gotta stand for something or you'll fall for anything ♪
♬我说，来吧，人们……♪
♪ I said, come on, people... ♪
你今天看起来很漂亮，是吧?
You're looking beautiful today, huh?
嘿…看到那边那些黄色的家伙了吗?
Hey...  You see those yellow fellas over there?
那是高畑先生。
That's Mr. Takahata.
他总是问奎妮要特别的菜单。
He always asks Queenie for the special menu.
我们有来自世界各地的女孩，伙计。
We've got girls from all over the world, man.
迪拜，俄罗斯，新加坡。
Dubai, Russia, Singapore.
有一道菜肴可以取悦每一位国王。看。
There's a dish to please every king. Look.
他即将收到来自天堂的礼物。
He's about to receive a gift from heaven.
她来了，西尔维娅。
Here she is-- Sylvia.
前立陶宛小姐。
Former Miss Lithuania.
她是来指引他到来世的。
She's come down to guide him to the afterlife.
来吧。
Come on.
这是殿下。
That's Mirza.
老板中的老板。
The boss of the bosses.
他掌管着镇上的一切，伙计。
He runs everything in this town, man.
药品、财产、进口、出口。
Drugs, property, import, export.
你说吧。
You name it.
警察怎么办?
What about the cops?
他们是最肮脏的混蛋。
They're the dirtiest fuckers.
你知道我的意思。
You know what I'm meaning.
拉纳酋长呢?
And Chief Rana?
在贵宾室。
Up in the VIP room.
他喜欢吃糖。
He loves the sugar.
她是不是很漂亮?
Isn't she beautiful?
我叫她尼基。
I call her Nicki.
·米娜雅一起作为颁奖嘉宾。
Minaj.
大保险杠，漂亮的前灯。
Big bumper, nice headlights.
嗯?拜托，兄弟。
Huh? Come on, brother.
让我们跳舞吧。
Let's boogie.
-系好安全带，伙计。-为什么?
- Seat belt, buddy. - What for?
这为。
This for.
♬呜，呜
♪ Whoo, whoo ♪
♬大师们♬
♪ Masterminds ♪
♬R-O-C，双m - g
♪ R-O-C, double-M-G ♪
♬杰，我知道了，我知道了
♪ Jay, I got it, I got it ♪
♬我脚上的鞋跟有四层
♪ Four stacks for the heels on my feet ♪
♬汽车座椅仍然散发着十把钥匙的味道
♪ Car seats still smelling like ten keys ♪
♬告诉插头，我在寻求增加♬
♪ Tell the plug that I'm lookin' for an increase ♪
♬停翼，胖男孩需要十件
♪ Wingstop, fat boy need a ten-piece ♪
♬说一个名字，汽车就启动了
♪ Say a name and the car start ♪
-♬切换，切换
- ♪ Switching, switching ♪
♬就像沃尔玛一样。♪
♪ Lane to lane like Walmart. ♪
你的手怎么了?
What happened to your hands?
他们糟透了，兄弟。
They're fucked up, bro.
车祸。发动机着火了。
Car crash. Engine caught fire.
废话。
Bullshit.
我知道那是什么。
I know what that is.
口袋弹球玩得太多了，是吧?
Too much pocket pinball, huh?
你知道我的意思。
You know what I'm meaning.
但你过着真正的生活，兄弟。
But you're living the life, bro.
我们现在要和国王们一起了，是吧?
We're rolling with the kings now, huh?
他们甚至看不见我们。
They don't even see us.
他们都在天上活着，而我们却困在这里。
They're all up there living, and we're stuck here in this.
那不是生活，兄弟。
That's no life, bro.
那你打算怎么办，猴人?嗯?
So, what are you gonna do about this, Monkey Man? Huh?
我在南边买了块地。
Bought myself a bit of land over here down south.
-你喜欢吗?——嗯。
- You like that? - Mm-hmm.
伴侣。
Mate.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
那是红酒。
That's red wine.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
嗯，那是一个白酒杯。
Well, that's a white wine glass.
-这家伙是谁啊?
- Who is this guy, huh?
能找个人过来一下吗?跟我说说你的旅行吧，宝贝。
Can we get somebody over here who knows... Tell me more about your trip, baby.
不。
No.
不不不不不不。
No, no, no, no, no.
我,嗯…我想了解你。
I, uh... I want to know about you.
这是什么?
What's this?
小小鸟吗?
Little birdie?
-是一只麻雀。-你想飞走吗?
-It's a sparrow. -Want to fly away, do you?
奎妮是对的。
Queenie was right.
你和其他女孩不一样。
You are not like the other girls.
我会像对待天使一样对待你。
I'll treat you like an angel.
-我的印度公主。
- My Indian princess.
我们可以在这里做爱。
We can fuck right here.
不是在这里，宝贝。
Not here, baby.
什么也不会发生。不要灰心。
Nothing will happen. Don't lose heart.
这块土地现在被宣布为圣地。
This land is now declared a holy site.
你们必须立即撤离!
You must vacate immediately!
这片土地属于我们的祖先。
This land belongs to our ancestors.
叫他把这些文件塞进屁眼!
Tell him to shove these papers up his ass!
我们的血液在土壤里!
Our blood is in the soil!
我们永远不会把这片土地给你。
We will never give you this land.
我们永远不会把这片土地给你!
We will never give you this land!
马!
Ma!
你是怎么进来的?
How did you get in?
不,不。来了。
No, no. Come.
来了,来了。好姑娘。
Come, come. Good girl.
好了。好了。好姑娘。
There you go. There you go. Good girl.
你喜欢吗?
You like that?
这很好。你喜欢吗?
That's good. You like that?
她最好。
She'd better.
一盘4000卢比。
It's 4,000 rupees a plate.
如果你不能处理这些事情，这就不是你工作的地方。
This is not the place to work if you can't handle that sort of stuff.
它不是麻雀。
It's not a sparrow.
你的纹身。
Your tattoo.
这是一个koel。
It's a koel.
我在森林里长大。
I grew up in the forest.
每天，我都会在他们的歌声中醒来。
Every day, I would wake up to them singing.
别再喂那条狗了。
Stop feeding that dog.
它会不断回来，期待更多。
It's gonna keep coming back expecting more.
只是给了她希望。
Just gives her hope.
下一个。
Next.
坐下。坐下。坐下。
Sit. Sit. Sit.
你他妈在干什么，伙计?
What the fuck you doing, man?
-为了狗。-拜托，伙计。让我们跳舞吧。
-For the dog. - Come on, man. Let's boogie.
坐下。
Sit.
Baba Shakti今天为正在进行的土地纠纷的受害者举行了一次公开祈祷，他主张暴力永远不是解决问题的办法。
Baba Shakti today held a public prayer for victims of the ongoing land disputes, advocating that violence is never the answer.
在其他地方，亚塔纳北部地区的跨性别居民被拍到遭到警察袭击。
Elsewhere, the transgender inhabitants in Yatana's northern district have been filmed being attacked by officers.
警察局长拉纳·辛格向公众保证，罪犯将被绳之以法。
Chief of Police Rana Singh assured the public that the culprits will be brought to justice.
你应该是一只猴子。
You're supposed to be a monkey.
你知道黑猩猩能把人的脸撕下来吗?
Do you know that a chimpanzee can rip a fucking human being's face off?
出去，他妈的表现得像只野兽。
Get out there and fucking behave like a fucking beast.
——检查。
- Check.
好姑娘。
Good girl.
好了。
There you go.
好姑娘。
Good girl.
你他妈的去哪了，伙计?
Where the fuck you been, man?
为了等你，我都快做完了。
I nearly finished it all waiting for you.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
-我们跳舞吧。
- Let's boogie.
这个家伙。来吧。
This guy. Come on.
嘿,Fresca。
Hey, Fresca.
给你带了个新男朋友。
Brought you a new boyfriend.
欢迎来到天堂，宝贝。
Welcome to heaven, baby.
《阁楼》。
Penthouse.
只有奎妮能上去。来吧。
Only Queenie can go up. Come on.
让自己忙碌起来。
Get busy.
Mwah。
Mwah.
♬你不必亮起红灯
♪ You don't have to put on the red light ♪
那些日子已经过去了
♪ Those days are over ♪
♬你不必把身体出卖给黑夜
♪ You don't have to sell your body to the night ♪
多汁的♬
♪ Juicy ♪
♬你今晚不必穿那条裙子
♪ You don't have to wear that dress tonight ♪
那些日子已经过去了
♪ Those days are over ♪
♬你不必亮起红灯
♪ You don't have to put on the red light ♪
多汁的♬
♪ Juicy ♪
那些日子已经过去了
♪ Those days are over ♪
♬你不必亮起红灯。♪
♪ You don't have to put on the red light. ♪
嘿,阿方索。让我们看看你的腿。
Hey, Alphonso. Show us your leg.
——嗯?
- Huh?
那混蛋想逃避毒品交易，所以他们把他砍了。
Fucker tried to run from a drug deal, so they chopped it off.
对吗?
Isn't that right?
告诉我一件事。
Tell me one thing.
你的鸡巴还能用吗?
Your dick still works, huh?
他不需要。他没胆。
He doesn't need one. He's got no balls.
滚开，去找我的猫。
Fuck off, go get my maal now.
在这里,先生。
Here, sir.
过来，宝贝。
Come here, baby.
♬当真相被发现时
♪ When the truth is found ♪
-是谎言
- ♪ To be lies ♪
你心中所有的快乐都消失了
♪ And all the joy within you dies ♪
难道你爱的人就不值得去爱吗?♪
♪ Don't you love somebody to love? ♪
♬你最好找个人来爱。♪
♪ You better find somebody to love. ♪
给我条毛巾，混蛋。
Gimme a towel, asshole.
这是什么鬼东西?
What the fuck is this?
来自母亲的祝福。
Blessings from my mother.
我希望你妈操得比你还狠。
I hope your mother fucks harder than you fight.
你他妈是谁，小老鼠?
Who the fuck are you, you little rat?
难道你不想有人来爱吗?♪
♪ Don't you want somebody to love? ♪
♬难道你不需要♬
♪ Don't you need ♪
♬有人要爱吗?♪
- ♪ Somebody to love? ♪
难道你不会爱吗
♪ Wouldn't you love ♪
♬有人要爱吗?♪
- ♪ Somebody to love? ♪
♬你最好找个人来爱
♪ You better find somebody to love ♪
——嘿!
- Hey!
-当真相被发现时
- ♪ When the truth is found ♪
♪成为谎言♪
♪ To be lies ♪
♬和所有的快乐
♪ And all the joy ♪
♬在你心中死去
♪ Within you dies ♪
-难道你不想吗
- ♪ Don't you want ♪
♬有人要去爱吗?♪
♪ Somebody to love? ♪
-难道你不需要
- ♪ Don't you need ♪
♬有人要去爱吗?♪
♪ Somebody to love? ♪
难道你不愿意去爱一个人吗?♪
♪ Wouldn't you love somebody to love? ♪
♬你最好找个人来爱。♪
♪ You better find somebody to love. ♪
拉苏尔!你他妈的在哪儿?
Rasul! Where the fuck are you?
袭击者就在停车场!
The attacker is in the parking lot!
醒醒吧，混蛋!
Wake up, asshole!
嘿!嘿!鲍比,等等!
Hey! Hey! Bobby, wait!
进入!
Get in!
那破车那么多，你就偷了我的?
Out of all the fucking cars in there, you stole mine?
阿方索，闭嘴!
Alphonso, shut up!
你他妈干了什么，伙计?
What the fuck did you do, man?
——操!他妈的!-你在想什么，伙计?
- Fuck! Fuck! - What were you thinking, man?
-天啊。他妈的,他妈的。——操!
- Oh, man. Fuck, fuck. - Fuck!
快停车!
Stop the vehicle now!
——啊,他妈的。
-Ah, fuck.
快停车!
Stop the car now!
我按什么键?-快他妈的把装备放下，兄弟!
What do I press? - Put the fucking gear, brother!
他妈的!
Fuck!
操,男人!
Fuck, man!
-鸭，鸭，鸭，鸭!——操!
- Duck, duck, duck, duck! - Fuck!
-妈的!哦，操，伙计!
- Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck, man!
他妈的!
-Fuck!
哦!
Oh!
他妈的。
Fuck.
涡轮!涡轮!
Turbo! Turbo!
他妈的!
Fuck!
他妈的。哦,男人。
Fuck. Oh, man.
-我们甩掉他们了吗?——开车!只是开车!
- Did we lose them? - Drive! Just drive!
-小心!
- Look out!
鲍比，起来，伙计。来吧。
Bobby, get up, man. Come on.
我很抱歉，兄弟。
I am sorry, bro.
我很抱歉。
I am sorry.
他是个固执的混蛋，不是吗?
Stubborn bastard, isn't he?
老板会生吞他的。
The boss is gonna eat him alive.
-他不会放过他的
- He's not going to spare him.
他妈的。
Fuck.
♬涂海美丽的幻想♬
♪ Tu hai meri fantasy ♪
♬呐呐，呐呐，呐呐，呐呐……♪
♪ Chhoona na, chhoona na, chhoona na, chhoona na... ♪
你想做爱吗?
You want to fuck, huh?
你想上床吗，混蛋?
You want to fuck, motherfucker, huh?
你把警察带到我家来了?
You bring the police to my place, huh?
你怎么敢。
How dare you.
嘿。一件容易的事。
Hey. Easy.
♬我想找一个人来做我想做的事
♪ Haaye chhua jo toone to dil ne maari seeti ♪
♬决定在加仑里相会相会相会相会
♪ Dede in gaalon pe ek pappi meethi meethi ♪
♬呵，呵，呵，呵，呵，呵，呵，呵
♪ Ho ho chhua jo toone to dil ne maari seeti ♪
♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪
♪ Dede dede in gaalon pe ek pappi meethi meethi ♪
♬你爱我，我爱你
♪ Yauvan tera saavan bhara ♪
♬祝你好运!♬
♪ Bheeg gaya dil yeh mera ♪
♬啊哈，啊哈，啊哈，啊哈，啊哈，啊哈，啊哈
♪ Aaha toone hi barsat karaayi kya kare yeh yauan ♪
-♬Bechara, Bechara, Bechara
- ♪ Bechara bechara bechara ♪
♬哦啦啦，哦啦啦♬
♪ Ooh la la, ooh la la ♪
哦啦啦，哦啦啦
- ♪ Ooh la la, ooh la la ♪
♬祝你幸福，祝你幸福
♪ Tu hai meri fantasy na na na ♪
从这里跑开!
Run away from here!
♬呐呐，呐呐
♪ Chhoona na, chhoona na ♪
♬Ab main jawan ho gayi…♪
♪ Ab main jawan ho gayi... ♪
警察!
Police!
这是最后一次警告!
This is your last warning!
看到目标了。
Target in sight.
我只崇拜你。
I only worship you.
你是最强大的。
You are the most powerful one.
你是我的救世主。
You are my saviour.
慢慢地，慢慢地，慢慢地。然后呢?
Slowly, slowly, slowly. And then?
你让我们用爱微笑。
You make us smile with love.
- - - ?-保守我们的心脱离罪恶。
- And? - Keep our hearts free from sin.
真的很好!
Really good!
我们要带一些回家吗?
Should we take some of these home?
是的,好的。
Yes, ok.
我用这个给你做酸辣酱。
I will make you chutney with this.
看看这些根，多结实啊。
Look at these roots and how strong they are.
你认为他们会去哪里?
Where do you think they go?
-我不知道。-在地下深处。
- I don't know. - Deep below the ground.
树根又是怎样从地里长出来的呢?
And how do the roots grow from the ground?
让我看看你的。
Show me yours.
这是第一个根。
This is the first root.
这是二次根。
This is the second root.
这是三次方根。
And this is the third root.
所以，我们的手也有根……它们告诉我们将来要做什么。
So, our hands also have roots... They tell us what we'll do in the future.
你将来会做什么?
What will you do in the future?
嗯…
Um...
你是好的。
You're okay.
你是醒着的。
You're awake.
最后。
Finally.
美丽。
Beautiful.
不是她?
Isn't she?
Parvati和Shiva。
Parvati and Shiva.
一半是奉献，一半是毁灭。
One half devotion, the other destruction.
男性。
Male.
女性。
Female.
既不。
Neither.
两者都有。
Both.
一些人发现……奇怪。
Some people find that... strange.
但是我们海吉拉完全理解。
But we hijras understand it completely.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是阿尔法，神庙的守护者。
I'm Alpha, the keeper of the temple.
——小心!小心!
- Careful! Careful!
你为什么帮我?
Why did you help me?
你应该死于那些伤。
You should've died from those injuries.
诸神对你一定有更伟大的安排。
The gods must have a greater plan for you.
我们都有伤疤。
We all have scars.
我该走了。
I should go.
不。我不会那么做的。
No. I wouldn't do that.
警察正在找你。
The police are looking for you.
到处都是。
All over town.
但不是在这里。
But not here.
他们也会找到我们……令人不安。
They find us too... unsettling.
别走开。
Stay with us.
休息。
Rest.
你需要疗伤。
You need to heal.
也许她会跟你说话。
Maybe she'll speak to you.
生命力!生命力!生命力!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
生命力!生命力!生命力!生命力!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
生命力!生命力!生命力!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
生命力!生命力!生命力!生命力!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
生命力!生命力!生命力!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
生命力!生命力!生命力!生命力!生命力!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
他是谁?
Who is he?
他是个无名小卒。
He's a nobody.
只是个来自贫民区的疯孩子。
Just some crazy kid from the gutter.
人们曾经这么说过我。
People once said that about me.
现在看看你。
And now look at you.
你是国家的雄狮。
You're the nation's lion.
你说他提到了他母亲。
You said he spoke of his mother.
别为他担心……他是个行尸走肉。
Don't worry about him... He's a walking corpse.
Rana……在生命的巨幅挂毯上，一个小小的余烬可以烧毁一切。
Rana... in the great tapestry of life, just one small ember can burn down everything.
关于他的想法必须被消灭。
The very idea of him has to be extinguished.
找到他。
Find him.
在你的无名小卒成为大人物之前。
Before your nobody becomes a somebody.
破坏之路始于一名恐怖分子企图谋杀亚塔纳的警察局长拉纳·辛格(Rana Singh)，此人伪装成警察的工作人员。
The trail of destruction started with a murder attempt on Yatana's chief of police, Rana Singh, by a terrorist posing as a member of staff.
全市范围内正在搜捕这名恐怖分子及其同伙。
A citywide manhunt is underway for the terrorist and his known associates.
即将到来的选举在该国最吉祥的日子举行，安全措施已经提高。
Security has been raised for the upcoming elections, which are occurring on the country's most auspicious day.
-谢谢。所以,呃…这是一对夫妻的故事……的丈夫。
- Thank you. -So, uh... This one is a story of husband and wife... Husband.
和妻子。
And wife.
-现在他们没事了。
- Now they are okay.
但是…
But...
这就是她和牧师私奔的原因。
And that is why she ran away with the priest.
有趣的,是吗?
Funny, huh?
还是睡不着?
Still can't sleep?
我从不睡觉。
I never sleep.
你脑子里的声音?
Voices in your head?
只有一个。
Just one.
她的尖叫。
Her scream.
它一直在我体内。
It's been inside me my whole life.
跟我来。
Come with me.
在他们把我们流放到这里之前，我们是战士。
We were warriors before they drove us into exile here.
《吠陀经》中提到了一棵据说是世界毁灭者湿婆神种下的树。
The Vedas speak of a tree that was supposedly planted by Lord Shiva, the destroyer of worlds.
我曾经和你一样。
I was once like you.
一个破碎的人。
A broken man.
童年恐惧的奴隶。
A slave to childhood terrors.
我明白了为了成长，你需要毁灭。
I learned that you need to destroy in order to grow.
为新生活创造空间。
To create space for new life.
嗯，开始吧。
Mm. Here we go.
它的根部含有一种强大的毒素。
Within its root lies a potent toxin.
我们用湿婆的三叉戟命名它为Trishul。
We call it Trishul after Shiva's trident.
它会把你切开。
It will cut you open.
只有虚弱的人才能从中受益。
Only a weakened man can benefit from this.
只有强壮的人才能活下来。
Only a strong man can survive it.
你准备好了吗?
Are you ready?
是的。
Yes.
痛苦……一旦教会了你，它就会离开你。
The pain... It will leave you once it's finished teaching you.
兄弟姐妹们!
Brothers and Sisters!
欢迎来到罗摩衍那的故事。
Welcome to the tale of the Ramayana.
每一代人都在重复这样的故事。
In each generation, the story repeats itself.
被俘的公主……还有她和魔王的战斗。
The captive Princess... And her fight with the Demon King.
我Ravan !
I'm Ravan!
邪恶的国王，请放了我。
Evil King, please let me go.
没人对我说不!
Nobody says no to me!
但后来!
But then!
然后大能者来了!
And then came the mighty one!
-妈妈，那是哈努曼!-是的。
- Mum, that's Hanuman! - Yes, it is.
接受我棍棒的第一击。
Take the first blow of my club.
感受我猴子的力量!
Feel my monkey strength!
我长尾猴!
I'm Hanuman!
说话。
Speak.
加油，拉纳，加油。
Go Rana, go.
是时候做上帝的工作了。
Time to do God's work.
他们回来。警察回来了。
They're back. The Police are back.
起床了。运行时,每一个人。
Get up. Run, everyone.
快点,快点。
Hurry, hurry.
快跑!我们必须撤离。是警察。
Run! We must evacuate. It's the Police.
听我说。
Listen to me.
你上楼躲起来。不要发出声音。
You go upstairs and hide. And don't make a sound.
不不，听我说。听我说。
No, no, listen to me. Listen to me.
上楼躲起来。不要发出任何声音。
Go upstairs and hide. And don't even make a slight sound.
但是你呢?
But what about you?
我不会有事的。
Nothing will happen to me.
就像老鼠躲起来一样?
Like how a mouse hides?
你像老鼠一样躲起来，不出声。
You hide like a mouse and make no sound.
你相信妈妈吗?
Do you trust Mum?
你相信我吗?
Do you trust me?
什么也不会发生。
Nothing will happen.
什么也不会发生。不要灰心。
Nothing will happen. Don't lose heart.
不要灰心。
Don't lose heart.
你是我的哈努曼。
You are my Hanuman.
很快。
Quickly.
很快,很快。
Quickly, quickly.
你建立了一个温馨的家。
You've built a sweet home.
你在外面说什么?
What were you saying outside?
嗯?
Huh?
把那些文件塞进你的屁股。
Shove those papers up your ass.
对吗?
Is that right?
该死的婊子!
Bloody whore!
你要把它塞进我屁股里?
You'll shove it up my ass, huh?
我示范给你看。
I'll show you.
起来，婊子。
Get up, bitch.
我辜负了她。
I failed her.
不。
No.
你想救她。
You tried to save her.
你会看到伤疤。
You see scars.
我看到了一个孩子为救母亲而奋斗的勇气。
I see the courage of a child fighting to save his mother.
这是一个注定要挑战众神的战士的双手。
These are the hands of a warrior who's destined to challenge the gods.
你一生都在努力感受痛苦。
All your life, you've been fighting to feel pain.
你需要为一个目标而奋斗。
You need to fight for a purpose.
战斗……为了我们所有人。
Fight... for all of us.
是时候记起你是谁了。
It's time to remember who you are.
随着主权党在民意调查中的支持率攀升，有指控称你破坏了200英亩林地来建造你的大型工厂。
As the Sovereign Party climbs in the polls, allegations have surfaced that you destroyed 200 acres of forestland to build your mega factory.
它不是工厂。
It's not a factory.
这是一个公社。
It's a commune.
那些流离失所的农民怎么办?
And what about the farmers that have been displaced?
啊。
Ah.
这片土地贫瘠而空旷。
The land was barren and empty.
住在那里的家庭很少加入这项事业。
Few families who lived there have joined the cause.
那些抱怨工作环境恶劣的工人呢?
And workers who complain of horrible working conditions?
他们不是工人。
They aren't workers.
他们是我的门徒。
They are my disciples.
-是的。
- Yeah.
嗯。
Hmm.
啊。
Ah.
起床了。
Get up.
在阿德什·乔希(Adesh Joshi)发表分裂言论后，全国各地爆发了教派暴力事件。
A surge of sectarian violence has exploded around the country after divisive remarks made by Adesh Joshi.
国际领导人谴责针对少数民族的暴力行为，但没有批评这位在民意调查中攀升的候选人。
International leaders have condemned the violence against minorities but have stopped short of criticizing the candidate as he climbs in the polls.
闭上眼睛，你会发现自己正坐在一棵高大的树上。
Close your eyes, and you will find yourself sitting atop a mighty tree.
这是你的家。
This is your home.
你是一头野兽。
You are a beast.
透过表面看下去，你会看到土壤深处的根，延伸得又远又广。
Look beneath the surface, and you will see roots deep under the soil, reaching far and wide.
这是你祖先的根，是你母亲的灵魂。
These are the roots of your ancestors, the soul of your mother.
听她的。
Listen to her.
你没什么好害怕的。
You have nothing to fear.
你在这里已经很久了。
You've been here for time.
Yatana的人们... ...巴巴生命力!
People of Yatana... ...Baba Shakti!
生命力!生命力!生命力!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
生命力!生命力!生命力!生命力!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
生命力!生命力!生命力!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
我什么都不是。
I am nobody.
I am nothing.
我没有选择这条路。
I didn't choose this path.
-你为我选的。
- You chose it for me.
没有斗争，变革就不会到来。
Change never comes without a fight.
我要你再选一个上帝的人。
I want you to choose another of God's men.
他是我们中的一员。他就是主权党领袖Adesh Joshi。
He's one of us. He is Adesh Joshi, leader of Sovereign Party.
他会和我们一起战斗，为了我们，为了你们。
He will fight with us, for us, for you.
工人，穷人，病人。
The working man, the poor, the sick.
用你的爱浇灌他，让我们的声音传遍全国。
Shower him with your love and let our voice be heard throughout the nation.
他们摧毁了我们神圣的价值观。
They have destroyed our sacred values.
他们偷走了我们的家园，毒害了我们孩子的心灵。
They have stolen our homes, poisoned our children's minds.
他们用他们的象征，他们虚假的偶像玷污了我们。
They have polluted us with their symbols, their false idols.
我们被蒙蔽了双眼。
We have been blinded.
你会和我们站在一起吗?
Will you stand with us?
你愿意和我们一起流血吗?
Will you bleed with us?
你会吗?
Will you?
印度母亲的胜利。
Victory for Mother India.
印度母亲的胜利!
Victory for Mother India!
拉克希米!
Lakshmi!
告诉我拉克希米怎么了。
Tell me what happened to Lakshmi.
——拉!——拉!
- Lakshmi! - Lakshmi!
——拉克希米。-你没事吧，拉克希米?
- Lakshmi. - Are you okay, Lakshmi?
发生了什么事?发生了什么事?
What happened? What happened?
这些人在门上贴了一张告示。
These men put a notice on the door.
她想把它取下来，但他们打了她。
She tried to take it down, but they beat her.
她没有呼吸了。呼吸，拉克希米，呼吸。
She's not breathing. Breathe, Lakshmi, breathe.
你看到了吗?你看到是谁了吗?
Did you see? Did you see who it was?
生命力的男人。
Shakti's men.
他们说神庙从来不属于我们。
They said the temple never belonged to us.
阿尔法，我们去哪?
Alpha, where will we go?
如果我们没有钱，他们会继续这样做。
If we don't have money, they will keep doing this.
我们不能收买那些暴徒。
We cannot pay off some thugs.
我们都必须祈祷。
We all must pray.
拉克希米!
Lakshmi!
上帝自有安排。
God has a plan.
排灯节期间我们将公布选举结果。
We have the election results due to break during Diwali festival.
主权党期待压倒性胜利的支持者涌上街头。
Sovereign Party supporters are flooding the streets with the party expecting a landslide victory.
爸爸!生命力!
-Baba! -Shakti!
——爸爸!——生命力!
- Baba! - Shakti!
——爸爸!爸爸!——生命力!生命力!
- Baba! Baba! - Shakti! Shakti!
女士们，先生们!
Ladies and gentlemen!
♬杰克扑腾，扑腾，杰克扑腾
♪ Jake puch le tu, puch puch puch, Jake puch le tu ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你，我爱你，我爱你
♪ Naam mera bolta mai kamm jyada bolta hai kaam mera ♪
你准备好打架了吗?
Are you ready for a fucking fight?
♬Hai zubaan-e-gulab甘蓝karam ki kitaab♬
♪ Hai zubaan-e-gulab kale karam ki kitaab ♪
♬我给了你工作，亲爱的，亲爱的
♪ Bhare gire jo shraab nasha dalta ♪
不，不，不，不，不
♪ Dbaav rhe tadipaar, bhag bhag bhag ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你
♪ Na kabhi jiya maraa boht baar ♪
♬哈哈，哈哈，哈哈，哈哈，哈哈，哈哈，哈哈，哈哈，哈哈
♪ Bhag bhag bhag, hai jo bhi dil me beta bol dal ♪
♬哈哈哈哈哈哈，哈哈哈哈，哈哈哈哈
♪ Bhag bhag bhag, hai alag mera khel ♪
把它放在猴子身上。
Put it on the monkey.
在我的左边，仍然是全印度无可争议的冠军，蛇……国王Kobra !
On my left, the still undisputed champion of all of India, - the s-s-s-s-snake... King Kobra!
♬耶达·马恩基·桑巴夫纳
♪ Jyada marne ki sambhavna ♪
♬Jeevan yeh samundar, yaha dubaadeti hai bhavna
♪ Jeevan yeh samundar, yaha dubaadeti hai bhavna ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你
♪ Dabte nhi usse jispe chlta apna davv na ♪
♬我爱你，我爱你，我爱你。♪
♪ Khaana kabhi maang na, nahi seekha dar se bhagna. ♪
国王Kobra !国王Kobra !
King Kobra! King Kobra!
-好吧，冷静点。
- Okay, settle down.
安静点，你们这些畜生。
Settle down, you animals.
-安定下来。
- Settle down.
从国王陛下一直到我母亲非洲最深最黑暗的丛林……我找到了他。
From His Majesty all the way to the deepest, darkest jungles of my mother Africa... I hunted him down.
我…-…是我亲自把他弄来的，我大老远把他带到这儿来给你看的。
I... - ...darted him myself, and I brought him all the way here for your entertainment.
他是邪恶的。
He's evil.
他是凶猛的。
He's ferocious.
他是黑暗毁灭者。
He's a dark destroyer.
我给你…香港!
I give you... Kong!
你想看这两只动物打架吗?
Do you want to see these two animals fight?
蛇和猴子。
The snake and the monkey.
战斗!
Fight!
国王Kobra !国王Kobra !
King Kobra! King Kobra!
国王Kobra !国王Kobra !国王Kobra !国王Kobra !
King Kobra! King Kobra! King Kobra! King Kobra!
哦，我闻到了。
Ooh, I smell it.
-我闻到了。
- I smell it.
-嗨。-怎么回事?
- Hey. - What's going on?
他把他打晕了吗?
Did he fucking knock him out?
科布拉，起来。
Kobra, get up.
你现在就把他揍趴下。
You get him fucking up right now.
我会操…抓住他的胳膊，把他弄下来。
I will fuck... Grab his arms and take him off.
哇,是吗?
Wow, eh?
哇。
Wow.
这是一个惊喜。
That was a surprise.
真他妈走运，是吧?
Fucking lucky kick, eh?
看来今晚有只顽皮的小猴子要来了。
Looks like we got a cheeky little monkey on our hands tonight.
杀了那野兽!
Kill the beast!
杀了那野兽!杀了那野兽!杀了那野兽!
Kill the beast! Kill the beast! Kill the beast!
-女士们先生们…我给你最大的，最坏的，粉碎骨头的熊巴鲁!
- Ladies and gentlemen... I give you the biggest, the baddest, the bone crushing Bhalu the Bear!
去他的。
Fuck him up.
打烂他的头，好吗?
Fucking smash his head in, okay?
进去揍他一顿。
Get in there and fucking pummel him.
——走吧。走了。
- Go. Go.
去他的。
Fuck him up.
打他的鸡巴!
Smack him in the fucking cock!
来吧!
Come on!
钻他!
Drill him!
把他的脑袋钻出来!
Drill his fucking skull in!
打他的脸!
Drill him in the fucking face!
来，揍他，巴鲁!
Go on, smack him, Bhalu!
那就来吧!
Come on, then!
继续，猴子人!是的!
Go on, Monkey Man! Yes!
杀了那野兽!杀了那野兽!
Kill the beast! Kill the beast!
杀了那野兽!杀了那野兽!杀了那野兽!杀了那野兽!
Kill the beast! Kill the beast! Kill the beast! Kill the beast!
杀了那野兽!杀了那野兽!杀了那野兽!
Kill the beast! Kill the beast! Kill the beast!
杀了那野兽!杀了那野兽!
Kill the beast! Kill the beast!
向大能者欢呼!
Hail the mighty one!
猴子万岁!
Hail Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
猴子的人!猴子的人!猴子的人!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
α。
Alpha.
看一看。
Take a look.
那是什么?
What is that?
看一看。
Take a look.
-有张纸条。-有张纸条。
- There's a note. - There's a note.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
哦，天哪，天哪。
Oh, my, my.
我是说，看看这个。
I mean, look at this.
——哇。
- Whoa.
-谁给我们送来的?——哇。
- Who sent us this? - Wow.
这是钱。
It's money.
爸爸!
Baba!
爸爸!爸爸!
Baba! Baba!
巴巴生命力!巴巴生命力!
Baba Shakti! Baba Shakti!
巴巴生命力!巴巴生命力!巴巴生命力!
Baba Shakti! Baba Shakti! Baba Shakti!
巴巴生命力!巴巴生命力!
Baba Shakti! Baba Shakti!
大家听好了，如果今晚有人搞砸了，如果有人搞砸了，如果有人抱怨，我就操死你们的幸福。
Listen up, everyone, if anybody fucks up tonight, if anybody messes up, if I get a single complaint, I'll fuck your happiness.
别盯着我看!第一道菜马上上桌!
Stop staring at me! First course out right now!
这是辉煌的。很好。
It's brilliant. Very good.
谢谢你！谢谢你！
Thank you. Thank you.
-谢谢。
- Thank you.
女士们先生们，很荣幸能在这里与君主党一起庆祝我们历史性的胜利。
Ladies and gentlemen, what an honor it is to be here with the Sovereign Party on the cusp of our historic victory.
总有一天，这些墙上的王公们会被你们每一个人的肖像所取代。
One day, the maharajas on these walls will be replaced with portraits - of each and every one of you.
嘿,自以为是的。
Hey, smart-ass.
工作人员入口。
Staff entrance.
我们将消除印度母亲的伤疤，让她再次美丽。
We will rid Mother India of her scars and make her beautiful once more.
我要感谢伟大的警察局长拉纳·辛格的伟大贡献。
I would like to acknowledge the great contribution of a mighty chief of police, Rana Singh.
他的勇气和正直使亚塔纳的犯罪率最低。
His courage and integrity has led to Yatana's lowest crime rate.
嘿!
Hey!
-该死!——屎!
- Oh, shit! - Shit!
♬在巴比伦的河边
♪ By the rivers of Babylon ♪
♬我们在那里坐了下来
♪ There we sat down ♪
♬是啊，我们哭了
♪ Yeah, we wept ♪
♬当我们想起锡安♬
♪ When we remembered Zion ♪
-那里有恶人
- ♪ There the wicked ♪
♬把我们囚禁起来♬
♪ Carried us away in captivity ♪
♬要求我们唱一首歌
♪ Required from us a song ♪
-现在我们该如何歌唱
- ♪ Now how shall we sing ♪
♬主的歌在…♪
♪ The Lord's song in a... ♪
还有另一个人，没有他的祝福，我们就不会在这里。
There is this one other person without whose blessing we would not be here.
我的大师。
My guru.
我的导师。
My mentor.
尊者，印度的雄狮，-巴巴沙克…
His Holiness, India's lion, - Baba Shak...
走吧!走吧!走吧!走吧!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
带他上楼。带他上楼。
Get him upstairs. Get him upstairs.
嘿!嘿!
Hey! Hey!
♬爱你，爱你，爱你，爱你
♪ De dana dan, de dana dan, de dana dan, de dana dan ♪
♬De, De, dem dana dan, De, De, De
♪ De, de, dem dana dan, de, de, de ♪
♬爱你，爱你，爱你
♪ De dana dan, de dana dan, de dana dan ♪
♪ De dana dan, de, de, de ♪
♬不，不，不
♪ De, de, de. ♪
走了。
Go.
你混蛋!
You motherfucker!
别惹我!
Don't fuck with me!
我要杀了你，你这个混蛋!
I'll kill you, you bastard!
我要炸了你…
I'm gonna blow your fucking...
终于从树上爬出来了?
Finally out of your tree, huh?
起床了。
Get up.
你妈妈让你回来要更多吗?
Did your mother send you back for more, huh?
起来，混蛋!
Get up, motherfucker!
你这个婊子养的。
You son of a whore.
你在看什么?
What are you looking at?
起来!
Get up!
欢迎,奎尼。
Welcome, Queenie.
那么，你就是那个人了?
So, you are the one?
看看他们所有人。
Look at them all.
排灯节。
Diwali.
光明战胜了黑暗。
The triumph of light over darkness.
击败拉万。
The defeat of Ravan.
但拉文不是恶魔。
But Ravan was no demon.
他是个学者。
He was a scholar.
一个有远见的人。
A visionary.
他白手起家建立了一个帝国。
He built an empire from nothing.
为什么不结束这种暴力循环?
Why not end this cycle of violence?
否则我们几代人都会被困在其中。
Or we will be trapped in it for generations.
你知道我妈妈叫什么吗?
Do you even know my mother's name?
你知道他们的名字吗?
Do you know any of their names?
愤怒不能平息你的灵魂，我的孩子。
Anger will not quiet your soul, my son.
别叫我儿子。"
Don't call me "son."
这是一个虔诚的追随者雕刻的，他戴着它们来防止他的脚伤害任何小生物。
These were carved by a devout follower who wore them to prevent his feet from harming any small creature.
在这一边，有一个古老的祈祷:
On the side here, there's an old prayer:
原谅我，大地之母，原谅我每一步都造成的伤害
"Forgive me, Mother Earth, for the sin of injury which I inflict with each step."
我的战车在这里。
My chariot is here.
你不能。这些人需要我。
You can't. These people need me.
请。
Please.
我会给你你想要的。
I'll give you what you want.
我愿意做任何事。
I'll do anything.
原谅我。
Forgive me.
哈哈，发发慈悲吧。
Ha-Ha-Have mercy, please.
现在只有上帝能原谅你了。
Only God can forgive you now.
哦，上帝，我崇拜你。
Oh God, I worship you.
我只崇拜你。
I only worship you.
你是最强大的。
You are the most powerful one.
你是我的救世主。
You are my saviour.
你让我们微笑。
You make us smile.
让我们的心充满爱。
And fill our hearts with love.
世界各地。在我心里。
All around the world. In my heart.
在我家。你无处不在。
In my home. You are everywhere.
每一根树根，每一滴水。
In every root, and every drop of water.
用我们的眼睛。用我们的耳朵。
With our eyes. With our ears.
在我们的唇边。我们叫你的名字。
On our lips. We say your name.
我昼夜歌颂你。
I sing your praise, day and night.
哦，上帝，我崇拜你。
Oh God, I worship you.
♪不要害怕♪
♪ Don't be afraid ♪
♬黑暗过后就是光明
♪ After the darkness is light ♪
所以不要害怕
♪ So don't you be afraid ♪
♬长夜来临了
♪ And there comes the long night ♪
♬哦，漫漫长夜
♪ Oh, long night ♪
♬要有信心♬
♪ Have faith ♪
♬一路前行♬
♪ Journey along ♪
如果你不知道
♪ If you don't know ♪
♬路很长
♪ The path is long ♪
但如果你尝试
♪ But if you try ♪
♬你一定会成长
♪ You'll surely grow ♪
♬治愈过去的悲伤
♪ To heal past the sorrow ♪
♬那让你一直很低落
♪ That been keeping you low ♪
♬你低，所以♬
♪ You low, so ♪
♬成长，成长，成长，成长
♪ Grow, grow, grow, grow ♪
-长大，长大
- ♪ Grow, grow ♪
♬成长，成长
♪ Grow, grow ♪
♬你必须成长
♪ You've got to grow ♪
-♬成长，成长，成长
- ♪ Grow, grow, grow ♪
即使只有你一个人
♪ Even if you're on your own ♪
即使你找不到自己的路
♪ Even if you can't find your way ♪
♪即使旅途寒冷♪
♪ Even if the journey is cold ♪
♪相信我到死♪
♪ Believe in I to death ♪
♬我知道你会成长
♪ And I know that you will grow ♪
一天又一天
♪ Day by day ♪
如果你与爱同行
♪ If you walk with love ♪
♬你们永远不会是陌生人
♪ You'll never be strangers ♪
-长大，长大
- ♪ Grow, grow ♪
成长吧，成长吧。♪
♪ Grow, grow. ♪
♬锦鲤给了锦鲤，锦鲤给了锦鲤
♪ Koi toh aake dede, koi toh aake dede ♪
♬Koi toake dede♬
♪ Koi toh aake dede ♪
一，二，三。
One, two, three.
♬锦鲤锦鲤锦鲤
♪ Koi koi koi ♪
♬锦鲤给了锦鲤，锦鲤给了锦鲤
♪ Koi toh aake dede, koi toh aake dede ♪
♬Koi toake dede♬
♪ Koi toh aake dede ♪
♬锦鲤给了锦鲤，锦鲤给了锦鲤
♪ Koi toh aake dede, koi toh aake dede ♪